



Sebastiano Girotto

Nationality: Italian Date of birth: 5 Nov 2005

Capacita Serie de la combane de la combane

Email address: sebastianogirotto05@gmail.com

▼ Twitter: https://twitter.com/ssebastianoo

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sebastianogirotto/

Website: https://gir8.it

• Home: Via Toni Benetton 2, 31021 Mogliano Veneto (TV) (Italy)

ABOUT ME

I've been dealing with technology since a young age, my curiosity for computers developed a strong passion for programming. I've been building personal projects to satisfy my needs since middle school. During the last years I worked with frontend tools for various people and companies. I love mixing technology with arts and music when producing beats or shooting a short film.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer

Freestyle In Venice Srl [Jun 2022 - Sep 2022]

City: Venezia | **Country:** Italy

Developed a Flask server that interacted with the Telegram API and storing data with MySQL

Freelance Frontend Developer

[Feb 2022 - Jun 2022]

City: Remote | Country: Italy

- Created websites from PDF references
- Designed and coded web apps
- Used frameworks like Next.js, SvelteKit and Astro
- Designed using Adobe products and Figma

Frontend Developer

M4SS [Jul 2023 - Oct 2023]

City: Reggio Emilia + Remote | Country: Italy

- Coded IoT frontend tools using JavaScript, TypeScript and SvelteKit
- Integrated APIs based on Rust and PostgreSQL on various frontends
- Designed dashboards and other web apps using Figma

Backend developer

Reply Totem

City: Remote | Country: Italy

Developed APIs that worked with Telegram and Discord to manage various tournaments for an eSports community using Python

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

High School

Liceo Artistico Statale Michelangelo Guggenheim [Sep 2019 - Current]

City: Venezia | Country: Italy | Website: https://www.liceoguggenheim.edu.it/ | Field(s) of study: Multimedia Arts

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Italian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Software Development

Python / JavaScript / PostgreSQL / TypeScript / MySQL / HTML / React / Flask / Node.js / SvelteKit / Next.js / CSS / Fi rebase / Astro.js

IT

Linux / Git / Docker

Design

Adobe Photoshop / Adobe Illustrator / Adobe Premiere Pro / Figma / Adobe After Effects